eyeofdubai.com 2009-05-30

# Privacy Policy - Eye of Dubai

**1\. Introduction  
**This policy covers the EYE OF DUBAI’S use of personal information that the EYE OF DUBAI collects when you use eyeofdubai.com the policy also gives you information about eye of Dubai - Fourth Dimension Co and third parties' use   
From time to time, you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself (e.g. name and email address…ETC) in order to receive or use services on our website. Such services include newsletters, competitions, Buy & Sell, Classifieds, message boards and eyeofdubai.com membership.  
By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable EYE OF DUBAI and its service providers to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy. When using your personal information EYE OF DUBAI will act in accordance with current legislation and aim to meet current Internet best practice.

**2\. Visitor Information  
**During the course of any visit to eyeofdubai.com, the pages you see, along with a short text file called a 'cookie', are downloaded to your computer. Many websites do this, because cookies enable website publishers to do useful things like find out whether the computer (and probably its user) has visited the website before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie left there on the last visit.  
Information supplied by cookies can help us to provide you with a better online user experience and assist us to analyze the profile of our visitors. For example: if on a previous visit you went to our Classifieds pages, we might find this out from your cookie and highlight Classifieds information on your second and subsequent visits.

**3\. What is a cookie?**  
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.  
Many sites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online traffic flows.  
Cookies record information about your online preferences. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalized services cannot then be provided to that user and accordingly you may not be able to take full advantage of all of EYE OF DUBAI features. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.  
If you have set your computer to reject cookies you can still browse EYE OF DUBAI anonymously until such time as you wish to register for eyeofdubai.com services. 

**4\. Use and storage of your personal information**  
When you supply any personal information to eyeofdubai.com (e.g. for competitions, eyeofdubai.com Community services or eyeofdubai.com membership) we have legal obligations towards you in the way we use those data. We must collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use it (see the notices on particular WebPages that let you know why we are requesting the information) and tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else.  
In general, any information you provide to the EYE OF DUBAI will only be used within EYE OF DUBAI and by its agents and service providers. Your information will be disclosed where we are obliged or permitted by law. Also, if you post or send offensive, inappropriate or objectionable content anywhere on or to eyeofdubai.com or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour on EYE OF DUBAI, EYE OF DUBAI can use whatever information that is available to it about you to stop such behaviour. This may involve informing relevant third parties such as your employer, school e-mail/Internet provider and law enforcement agencies about the content and your behaviour.  
We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met, or, in the case of eyeofdubai.com membership you no longer wish to continue your registration as eyeofdubai.com member. For safety reasons, however, EYE OF DUBAI may store messaging transcript data (including message content, member names, times and dates) arising from the use of eyeofdubai.com Community services such as Connector for a period of six months. Where personal information is held for people who are not yet registered but have taken part in other eyeofdubai.com services (e.g. forums, VIP club), that information will be held as long as is necessary to ensure that the service is run smoothly. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with UAE laws.  
If you are notified on eyeofdubai.com site that your information may be used to allow the EYE OF DUBAI to contact you for "service administration purposes", this means that the EYE OF DUBAI may contact you for a number of purposes related to the service you have signed up for. For example, we may wish to provide you with password reminders or notify you that the particular service has been suspended for maintenance. We will not contact you for promotional purposes, such as notifying you of improvements to the service or new services on eyeofdubai.com unless you specifically agree to be contacted for such purposes at the time you submit your information on the site, or at a later time if you sign up specifically to receive such promotional information, all of that depends on your requests. 

**5\. Access to your personal information  
**You have the right to request a copy of the personal information EYE OF DUBAI holds about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Please send email to [info@eyeofdubai.com](mailto:info@eyeofdubai.com)

**6\. Users 16 and under**  
If you are aged 16 or under, please get your parent/guardian's permission beforehand whenever you provide personal information to the **EYE OF DUBAI** 's website. 

**7\. How to find and control your cookies**  
If you're using **Netscape 6.0** :  
On your Task Bar, click:   
1. Edit, then   
2. Preferences   
3. Click on Advanced   
4. Click on Cookies   
If you're using Internet Explorer 6.0:   
1. Choose Tools, then   
2. Internet Options   
3. Click the Privacy Tab   
4. Click on Custom Level   
5. Click on the 'Advanced' button   
6. Check the 'override automatic cookie handing' box and select Accept, Block or Prompt for action as appropriate. 

If you're using **Internet Explorer 5.0 or 5.5** :   
1. Choose Tools, then   
2. Internet Options   
3. Click the Security tab   
4. Click on Custom Level   
5. Scroll down to the sixth option to see how cookies are handled by IE5 and change to Accept, Disable, or Prompt for action as appropriate. 

If you're using **Internet Explorer 4.0** :   
1. Choose View, then   
2. Internet Options   
3. Click the Advanced tab   
4. Scroll down to the yellow exclamation icon under Security and choose one of the three options to regulate your use of cookies. 

If you're using **Internet Explorer 3.0** :  
You can View, Options, Advanced, then click on the button that says Warn before Accepting Cookies. 

If you're using **Netscape Communicator 4.0** :  
On your Task Bar, click:   
1. Edit, then   
2. Preferences   
3. Click on Advanced   
4. Set your options in the box that says Cookies. 

**8\. How do you know which of the sites you've visited use cookies?**  
If you're using **Netscape 6.0** :  
On your Task Bar, click:   
1. Edit, then   
2. Preferences   
3. Click on Advanced   
4. Click on Cookies   
5. Click the View Cookies button 

If you're using **Internet Explorer 5.0 or 6.0** :   
1. Choose Tools, then   
2. Internet Options   
3. Click the General tab   
4. Click Settings   
5. View Files 

If you're using **Internet Explorer 4.0** :  
On your Task Bar, click:   
1. View, then   
2. Internet Options   
3. Under the tab General (the default tab) click   
4. Settings   
5. View Files. 

If you're using **Internet Explorer 3.0** :  
On your Task Bar, click:   
1. View   
2. Options   
3. Advanced   
4. View Files. 

If you're using **Netscape Communicator 4.0** :  
Netscape bundles all cookies into one file on your hard drive. You'll need to find the file, which it calls Cookie.txt on Windows machines.

**9\. How to see your cookie code  
**Just click on a cookie to open it. You'll see a short string of text and numbers. The numbers are your identification card, which can only be seen by the server that gave you the cookie.

FOURTH DIMENSION CO  
/ EYE OF DUBAI / © 2003-2008  
DUBAI - UAE
